{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037598399","data":{"timestamp":" 947037598399"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 2394cc01-e1ea-46d7-a71b-7e17086aeb9d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037600482","data":{"timestamp":" 947037600482"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 2394cc01-e1ea-46d7-a71b-7e17086aeb9d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037602554","data":{"timestamp":" 947037602554"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 2394cc01-e1ea-46d7-a71b-7e17086aeb9d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037605691","data":{"timestamp":" 947037605691"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 2394cc01-e1ea-46d7-a71b-7e17086aeb9d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037607875","data":{"timestamp":" 947037607875"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 2394cc01-e1ea-46d7-a71b-7e17086aeb9d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037610074","data":{"timestamp":" 947037610074"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 2394cc01-e1ea-46d7-a71b-7e17086aeb9d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037612913","data":{"timestamp":" 947037612912"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 2394cc01-e1ea-46d7-a71b-7e17086aeb9d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037615118","data":{"timestamp":" 947037615117"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 2394cc01-e1ea-46d7-a71b-7e17086aeb9d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037617324","data":{"timestamp":" 947037617324"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 2394cc01-e1ea-46d7-a71b-7e17086aeb9d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037620587","data":{"timestamp":" 947037620587"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 2394cc01-e1ea-46d7-a71b-7e17086aeb9d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037622649","data":{"timestamp":" 947037622648"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 2394cc01-e1ea-46d7-a71b-7e17086aeb9d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037624756","data":{"timestamp":" 947037624755"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 2394cc01-e1ea-46d7-a71b-7e17086aeb9d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037627780","data":{"timestamp":" 947037627779"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 2394cc01-e1ea-46d7-a71b-7e17086aeb9d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037630026","data":{"timestamp":" 947037630026"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 2394cc01-e1ea-46d7-a71b-7e17086aeb9d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037632276","data":{"timestamp":" 947037632276"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 2394cc01-e1ea-46d7-a71b-7e17086aeb9d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037635303","data":{"timestamp":" 947037635303"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 2394cc01-e1ea-46d7-a71b-7e17086aeb9d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037637401","data":{"timestamp":" 947037637400"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 2394cc01-e1ea-46d7-a71b-7e17086aeb9d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037637476","data":{"timestamp":" 947037637476"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 2394cc01-e1ea-46d7-a71b-7e17086aeb9d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037660225","data":{"timestamp":" 947037660224"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 711b0c40-8ccc-4dba-9a63-c2e4e1361d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037660609","data":{"timestamp":" 947037660608"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 711b0c40-8ccc-4dba-9a63-c2e4e1361d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037661104","data":{"timestamp":" 947037661103"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 711b0c40-8ccc-4dba-9a63-c2e4e1361d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037661464","data":{"timestamp":" 947037661463"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 711b0c40-8ccc-4dba-9a63-c2e4e1361d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037661880","data":{"timestamp":" 947037661879"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 711b0c40-8ccc-4dba-9a63-c2e4e1361d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037662366","data":{"timestamp":" 947037662365"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 711b0c40-8ccc-4dba-9a63-c2e4e1361d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037662600","data":{"timestamp":" 947037662599"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 711b0c40-8ccc-4dba-9a63-c2e4e1361d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037665861","data":{"timestamp":" 947037665860"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 711b0c40-8ccc-4dba-9a63-c2e4e1361d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037665894","data":{"timestamp":" 947037665894"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 711b0c40-8ccc-4dba-9a63-c2e4e1361d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037666620","data":{"timestamp":" 947037666619"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 711b0c40-8ccc-4dba-9a63-c2e4e1361d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037667022","data":{"timestamp":" 947037667021"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 711b0c40-8ccc-4dba-9a63-c2e4e1361d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037667327","data":{"timestamp":" 947037667326"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 711b0c40-8ccc-4dba-9a63-c2e4e1361d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037667547","data":{"timestamp":" 947037667546"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 711b0c40-8ccc-4dba-9a63-c2e4e1361d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037667740","data":{"timestamp":" 947037667740"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 711b0c40-8ccc-4dba-9a63-c2e4e1361d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037668055","data":{"timestamp":" 947037668055"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 711b0c40-8ccc-4dba-9a63-c2e4e1361d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037668279","data":{"timestamp":" 947037668279"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 711b0c40-8ccc-4dba-9a63-c2e4e1361d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037671435","data":{"timestamp":" 947037671435"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 711b0c40-8ccc-4dba-9a63-c2e4e1361d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037671838","data":{"timestamp":" 947037671838"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 711b0c40-8ccc-4dba-9a63-c2e4e1361d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037674331","data":{"timestamp":" 947037674331"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 711b0c40-8ccc-4dba-9a63-c2e4e1361d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037674542","data":{"timestamp":" 947037674541"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 711b0c40-8ccc-4dba-9a63-c2e4e1361d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037674753","data":{"timestamp":" 947037674752"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 711b0c40-8ccc-4dba-9a63-c2e4e1361d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037678251","data":{"timestamp":" 947037678250"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 711b0c40-8ccc-4dba-9a63-c2e4e1361d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037682002","data":{"timestamp":" 947037682002"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 711b0c40-8ccc-4dba-9a63-c2e4e1361d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037683026","data":{"timestamp":" 947037683026"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 711b0c40-8ccc-4dba-9a63-c2e4e1361d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037685699","data":{"timestamp":" 947037685698"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 711b0c40-8ccc-4dba-9a63-c2e4e1361d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037686073","data":{"timestamp":" 947037686073"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 711b0c40-8ccc-4dba-9a63-c2e4e1361d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037686557","data":{"timestamp":" 947037686557"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 711b0c40-8ccc-4dba-9a63-c2e4e1361d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037686901","data":{"timestamp":" 947037686901"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 711b0c40-8ccc-4dba-9a63-c2e4e1361d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037687313","data":{"timestamp":" 947037687313"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 711b0c40-8ccc-4dba-9a63-c2e4e1361d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037687788","data":{"timestamp":" 947037687788"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 711b0c40-8ccc-4dba-9a63-c2e4e1361d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037688011","data":{"timestamp":" 947037688011"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 711b0c40-8ccc-4dba-9a63-c2e4e1361d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037691212","data":{"timestamp":" 947037691211"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 711b0c40-8ccc-4dba-9a63-c2e4e1361d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037691254","data":{"timestamp":" 947037691253"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 711b0c40-8ccc-4dba-9a63-c2e4e1361d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037691984","data":{"timestamp":" 947037691983"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 711b0c40-8ccc-4dba-9a63-c2e4e1361d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037692392","data":{"timestamp":" 947037692391"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 711b0c40-8ccc-4dba-9a63-c2e4e1361d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037692703","data":{"timestamp":" 947037692702"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 711b0c40-8ccc-4dba-9a63-c2e4e1361d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037692919","data":{"timestamp":" 947037692918"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 711b0c40-8ccc-4dba-9a63-c2e4e1361d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037693128","data":{"timestamp":" 947037693127"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 711b0c40-8ccc-4dba-9a63-c2e4e1361d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037693443","data":{"timestamp":" 947037693443"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 711b0c40-8ccc-4dba-9a63-c2e4e1361d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037693666","data":{"timestamp":" 947037693666"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 711b0c40-8ccc-4dba-9a63-c2e4e1361d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037696269","data":{"timestamp":" 947037696268"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 711b0c40-8ccc-4dba-9a63-c2e4e1361d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037696366","data":{"timestamp":" 947037696366"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 711b0c40-8ccc-4dba-9a63-c2e4e1361d95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.48__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037731840","data":{"timestamp":" 947037731840"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" f60fe296-a0b7-4583-9d27-f1028c46e2b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" iliki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKI"," userResponse":" ILIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.48__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037739328","data":{"timestamp":" 947037739328"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" f60fe296-a0b7-4583-9d27-f1028c46e2b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" iliki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKI"," userResponse":" START_ILIKI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.48__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037744451","data":{"timestamp":" 947037744451"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" f60fe296-a0b7-4583-9d27-f1028c46e2b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" iliki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKI"," userResponse":" START_ILIKI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.48__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037745972","data":{"timestamp":" 947037745972"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" f60fe296-a0b7-4583-9d27-f1028c46e2b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" iliki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.48__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037747549","data":{"timestamp":" 947037747549"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" f60fe296-a0b7-4583-9d27-f1028c46e2b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ishara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ISHARA"," userResponse":" ISHARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.48__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037752430","data":{"timestamp":" 947037752430"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" f60fe296-a0b7-4583-9d27-f1028c46e2b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ishara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ISHARA"," userResponse":" ISHARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.48__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037753990","data":{"timestamp":" 947037753990"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" f60fe296-a0b7-4583-9d27-f1028c46e2b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ingia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INGIA"," userResponse":" INGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.48__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037758048","data":{"timestamp":" 947037758048"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" f60fe296-a0b7-4583-9d27-f1028c46e2b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ingia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INGIA"," userResponse":" INGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.48__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037759613","data":{"timestamp":" 947037759612"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" f60fe296-a0b7-4583-9d27-f1028c46e2b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.48__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037762560","data":{"timestamp":" 947037762559"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" f60fe296-a0b7-4583-9d27-f1028c46e2b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.48__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037764154","data":{"timestamp":" 947037764153"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" f60fe296-a0b7-4583-9d27-f1028c46e2b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" imba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMBA"," userResponse":" IMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.48__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037767578","data":{"timestamp":" 947037767578"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" f60fe296-a0b7-4583-9d27-f1028c46e2b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" imba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.48__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037769176","data":{"timestamp":" 947037769175"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" f60fe296-a0b7-4583-9d27-f1028c46e2b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ikulu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKULU"," userResponse":" IKULU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.48__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037773617","data":{"timestamp":" 947037773617"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" f60fe296-a0b7-4583-9d27-f1028c46e2b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ikulu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKULU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.48__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037775212","data":{"timestamp":" 947037775211"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" f60fe296-a0b7-4583-9d27-f1028c46e2b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" imejaa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEJAA"," userResponse":" IMEJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.48__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037780235","data":{"timestamp":" 947037780235"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" f60fe296-a0b7-4583-9d27-f1028c46e2b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" imejaa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEJAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.48__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037782271","data":{"timestamp":" 947037782269"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" f60fe296-a0b7-4583-9d27-f1028c46e2b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" imejaa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037782507","data":{"timestamp":" 947037782507"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" f60fe296-a0b7-4583-9d27-f1028c46e2b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.48__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" imejaa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEJAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037823503","data":{"timestamp":" 947037823503"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" bc9a6d92-1b2a-4894-b5ca-54aafeab12fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_e-i-a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037832259","data":{"timestamp":" 947037832258"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" bc9a6d92-1b2a-4894-b5ca-54aafeab12fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_l-a-i"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037836552","data":{"timestamp":" 947037836552"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" bc9a6d92-1b2a-4894-b5ca-54aafeab12fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_v-z-i"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037841066","data":{"timestamp":" 947037841066"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" bc9a6d92-1b2a-4894-b5ca-54aafeab12fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-ch-p"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037851526","data":{"timestamp":" 947037851525"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" bc9a6d92-1b2a-4894-b5ca-54aafeab12fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_h-z-i"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037856680","data":{"timestamp":" 947037856679"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" bc9a6d92-1b2a-4894-b5ca-54aafeab12fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_l-i-g"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037860872","data":{"timestamp":" 947037860871"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" bc9a6d92-1b2a-4894-b5ca-54aafeab12fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_ch-n-i"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037865003","data":{"timestamp":" 947037865003"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" bc9a6d92-1b2a-4894-b5ca-54aafeab12fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_g-i-d"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037871801","data":{"timestamp":" 947037871801"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" bc9a6d92-1b2a-4894-b5ca-54aafeab12fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-p-n"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037876111","data":{"timestamp":" 947037876111"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" bc9a6d92-1b2a-4894-b5ca-54aafeab12fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_a-r-i"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037881901","data":{"timestamp":" 947037881900"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" bc9a6d92-1b2a-4894-b5ca-54aafeab12fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_i_a-r-i"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947037991137","data":{"timestamp":" 947037991136"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" bc9a6d92-1b2a-4894-b5ca-54aafeab12fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_i_a-r-i"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038042270","data":{"timestamp":" 947038042270"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" ff8a2f4c-5264-4577-a97d-67559438b8b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_t-i-d"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038061688","data":{"timestamp":" 947038061687"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" ff8a2f4c-5264-4577-a97d-67559438b8b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_l-y-i"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038243422","data":{"timestamp":" 947038243422"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" ff8a2f4c-5264-4577-a97d-67559438b8b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_f-i-y"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038255923","data":{"timestamp":" 947038255922"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" ff8a2f4c-5264-4577-a97d-67559438b8b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-u-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038271193","data":{"timestamp":" 947038271193"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" ff8a2f4c-5264-4577-a97d-67559438b8b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_r-z-i"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038275976","data":{"timestamp":" 947038275976"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" ff8a2f4c-5264-4577-a97d-67559438b8b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_n-f-i"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038280435","data":{"timestamp":" 947038280435"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" ff8a2f4c-5264-4577-a97d-67559438b8b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_d-i-a"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038286284","data":{"timestamp":" 947038286284"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" ff8a2f4c-5264-4577-a97d-67559438b8b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-e-l"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038290624","data":{"timestamp":" 947038290624"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" ff8a2f4c-5264-4577-a97d-67559438b8b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-k-b"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038296200","data":{"timestamp":" 947038296200"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" ff8a2f4c-5264-4577-a97d-67559438b8b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_r-i-a"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038303242","data":{"timestamp":" 947038303242"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" ff8a2f4c-5264-4577-a97d-67559438b8b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_r-i-a"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038309015","data":{"timestamp":" 947038309014"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" ff8a2f4c-5264-4577-a97d-67559438b8b5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_i_r-i-a"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038329913","data":{"timestamp":" 947038329912"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 04bcb98a-188a-48bd-b3c8-a2210d3a6d7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038332649","data":{"timestamp":" 947038332649"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 04bcb98a-188a-48bd-b3c8-a2210d3a6d7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038334264","data":{"timestamp":" 947038334263"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 04bcb98a-188a-48bd-b3c8-a2210d3a6d7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038337556","data":{"timestamp":" 947038337555"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 04bcb98a-188a-48bd-b3c8-a2210d3a6d7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038339170","data":{"timestamp":" 947038339169"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 04bcb98a-188a-48bd-b3c8-a2210d3a6d7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038341407","data":{"timestamp":" 947038341406"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 04bcb98a-188a-48bd-b3c8-a2210d3a6d7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038343004","data":{"timestamp":" 947038343003"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 04bcb98a-188a-48bd-b3c8-a2210d3a6d7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038345191","data":{"timestamp":" 947038345190"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 04bcb98a-188a-48bd-b3c8-a2210d3a6d7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038346799","data":{"timestamp":" 947038346798"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 04bcb98a-188a-48bd-b3c8-a2210d3a6d7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038352416","data":{"timestamp":" 947038352415"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 04bcb98a-188a-48bd-b3c8-a2210d3a6d7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038354049","data":{"timestamp":" 947038354049"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 04bcb98a-188a-48bd-b3c8-a2210d3a6d7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038357705","data":{"timestamp":" 947038357704"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 04bcb98a-188a-48bd-b3c8-a2210d3a6d7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038359319","data":{"timestamp":" 947038359318"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 04bcb98a-188a-48bd-b3c8-a2210d3a6d7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038363094","data":{"timestamp":" 947038363093"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 04bcb98a-188a-48bd-b3c8-a2210d3a6d7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038364697","data":{"timestamp":" 947038364697"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 04bcb98a-188a-48bd-b3c8-a2210d3a6d7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038386549","data":{"timestamp":" 947038386548"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 04bcb98a-188a-48bd-b3c8-a2210d3a6d7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038388156","data":{"timestamp":" 947038388156"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 04bcb98a-188a-48bd-b3c8-a2210d3a6d7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038390870","data":{"timestamp":" 947038390870"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 04bcb98a-188a-48bd-b3c8-a2210d3a6d7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038392477","data":{"timestamp":" 947038392476"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 04bcb98a-188a-48bd-b3c8-a2210d3a6d7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038398496","data":{"timestamp":" 947038398496"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 04bcb98a-188a-48bd-b3c8-a2210d3a6d7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038398606","data":{"timestamp":" 947038398606"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 04bcb98a-188a-48bd-b3c8-a2210d3a6d7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038421626","data":{"timestamp":" 947038421626"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 944948bd-009a-4a7b-a092-bd4972356e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038422655","data":{"timestamp":" 947038422655"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 944948bd-009a-4a7b-a092-bd4972356e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038424176","data":{"timestamp":" 947038424175"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 944948bd-009a-4a7b-a092-bd4972356e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038424239","data":{"timestamp":" 947038424239"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" 944948bd-009a-4a7b-a092-bd4972356e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038458122","data":{"timestamp":" 947038458122"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" fddfca46-c4a6-42ca-b2a5-d2a57a011e37"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038464508","data":{"timestamp":" 947038464508"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" fddfca46-c4a6-42ca-b2a5-d2a57a011e37"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_t-n-b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038470578","data":{"timestamp":" 947038470578"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_045943"," gameId":" fddfca46-c4a6-42ca-b2a5-d2a57a011e37"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_b_t-n-b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}